聊天发短信请靠边
Pull over to talk or text.
唔  这块焦糖烧肉真是太好吃了
Mmm! Gotta love a brown sugar glaze.
走廊内严禁饮食
No eating in the halls.
我忍不住啊  教练
I can't help it, coach.
这肉真叫入口即化
Just falls off the bone.
你拿的好像是上等的烤牛排啊
That's some solid-looking barbecue you got there.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是看《烧烤月刊》上的步骤做的
I followed a recipe from "Barbecue Monthly."
哎呀  黑胡椒放多了
Oh! Too much black pepper.
烧烤真是一门高深的艺术啊
Ah, it was all so confusing.
我爸爸是个
My father's...
素食主义者
A vegetarian.
我一直缺少一位烧烤方面的导师
I just have no one to guide me.
呃  不是我故意炫耀
Well, I don't like to brag,
但是去年夏天我确实在
but last summer I did win
史蒂文斯波因特烧烤比赛中拔得头筹
the Stevens Point "Thrilla on the Grilla" cook-off.
太棒了  鲁尼教练果然吃了烧烤这一套
Oh, yeah! Coach Rooney took the barbecue bait.
但是为什么他对我的发型只字未提
But seriously, not one word about the haircut?
这不是白弄了么
What gives?